

Mohammed Azmath

Phone: +91 8801222277
Email: azmathreal@gmail.com

Career Objective

With high expertise in management and decade long extensive experience in sales, business development, administration my strengths capitalizes in strategic planning, team building, and resource management. I have a long history of achievements in developing and implementing successful strategies.

Profile Summary

.A dedicated regional head liaison with all departments with over 12 years of extensive experience showcasing leadership through out my endeavour building client rapports and relationships with strong ability to improve efficiency, profits and identify areas that can be enhanced.

Work Experience

March 2023 - Present

Regional Head

Sportify - Education & Management Services Pvt Ltd Hyderabad - Telangana

Roles Responsibilites:-

- Identify Partnership opportunities in region.
- Prepare and present compelling business proposals to potential clients and partners.
- Revenue prospecting, recruit, on board partners.
- Close working with Head of operations on deliverable s.
- Build and implement strategies to increase new & existing business.
- Driving sales through B2B and business development.
- Build sales plan with end to end road map and execution.
- Develop strategic partnerships establish and maintain relationships with key stakeholders ,Negotiate and close partnership agreements.
- Collaborate with internal teams work closely with marketing, sales and operations teams on key deliverable.
- Build and maintain a strong pipeline of prospective clients.
- Creating quarterly and half yearly sales pipelines and funnel .
- Provide management with timely MIS reports on sales activities, targets, and achievements.
- Lead Generation, Management.
- Conversion ratio analysis, Alternative conversion plans.

March 2020 - February 2023

Senior Manager - Business Development

Topper Technologies

Hyderabad - Telangana

Roles Responsibilites:-

- Providing and driving sales through BDM's.
- Coordinating for Students On Boarding's.
- Coordinating team meetings, Training and addressing ground level challenges for improving performances.
- Weekly/ monthly meetings and subscriptions.
- Managing sales force and deliverables.
- driving operational excellence Sales Unit.
- Balancing people skills and operations management effectively.
- To be the Think Tank for the team by constantly developing new initiatives that increase the efficiency and effectiveness of the department.

- To act as the critical link between Sales and other linked departments (Marketing, Planning, Customer Care, HR and Other Functions).
- To evaluate and optimize the effectiveness by intelligent sales force allocation.
- To review new product development, market research and brand strategy

June 2017 - February 2020

Sr Program Manager

GUS Education India Hyderabad - Telangana

Roles & Responsibilities :-

- Education and Career Presentations.
- Quality Leads Generation, Qualifying and Management.
- · Leads to Conversion Ratio analysis.
- TPO's and SPOC Management.
- Revenue generation.
- · Creating Sales Plans and Pipelines ensuring timely achievement
- · MIS Reports .
- · Leading Student advisors and Counselors.
- Training centre identification, tie-ups and sign ups.
- Affiliate Partners tie-ups & sign ups.
- · Initiating Partner Orientation Programs.
- · Tutors identification, Sign ups and management.
- Driving business from B2B and B2C both.
- Team Handling, Team Management training and development.

June 2013 - May 2017

Regional Manager

People Combine Educational Imitative (Oakridge International School) Hyderabad - Telangana

Roles & Responsibilities :-

- · Driving Sales through in depth ATL & BTL.
- Lead Generation through Field visits to preschools of Oi Coco's & franchises and others.
- · Pre school tie-ups and events .
- Promotions planning organizing and management.
- Driving walk-ins and admissions
- New tie-ups, MOU signing and Retention.
- Plan and manage events Know Your Curriculum (KYC), Special Windows Emailers & Spot Registrations.
- Initiate Engagement Programs.
- Initiate organize and execute workshops.
- Facilitate Annual and Sports Programs at Campus for brand visibility.
- Identification and tie-up with day care within corporate premises.
- · top Gated Communities Events.
- Team induction, Management and training.

June 2011 - May 2013

Senior Business Development Manager

Mania The Princeton Review Hyderabad - Telangana

Roles & Responsibilities:

- Ensuring profits for all 7centers in Hyderabad.
- Business Seminar, Presentations and proposals.
- Planning and execution of all ATL& BTL activities.
- Marketing, Sales, Centre manager Team Management
- Working on teams Plan vs Actual ensuring 90 percent achievements.
- Centres Sales & Servicing audits.
- Close working on source and work closely with it.
- Planning, Execution and management of all test drives in Hyderabad.
- Centres Pre Launch Activities and executions.
- Working on sponsorship to drive sales.
- Working on databases and filtering.
- · Leads tracking, Qualifying and its management.
- Organizing various campaigns and Olympiads.

June 2006 - May 2011

Business Development Manager

Celestial SAP Labs Limited Hyderabad - Telangana

Roles & Responsibilities:

- Providing direction to the Business Development Department on a variety of business development activities to include proposal development, client relations, and account management.
- Placing qualified agents on in house implementation...
- Close interaction with the project management team for project requirement.
- Forming teams for marketing and sales.
- Relationship Management.
- Networking with the consultants and client companies.
- Proposal, presentations and follow ups.
- Relationship Management.
- Prepare sales pipelines.

EDUCATION

Masters, Business Administration(MBA)

AUCBM Osmania University Hyderabad, Telangana

Bachelor Computer Application(BCA)

Madina Degree & PG College Osmania University Hyderabad, Telangana

10+2

St Georges Boys Junior College Hyderabad , Telangana Graduated, May 2000 Graduated, July 2005 Marks 60% Division 1st

Graduated, July 2003 Marks 76% Division 1

Marks 65% Divisioin

COMPUTER PROFICIENCY

Operating System

Software

Microsoft Windows

 MS Office Word, Excel Power Point

LANGUAGES

- EnglishHindi
- Telugu

PERSONAL

Name : Mohammed Azmath

Father's Name Mohammed Barkat

Date of Birth/Age 23-may-1981/42 yrs.

Religion : Islam

Marital status Married

Address 12-2-422/67

> Priya Colony, Mehdipatnam , Hyderabad 500028